anonymster.com 2017-09-30

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to outline how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

 **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

 **When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.  
**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

• To send periodic emails regarding our services.  
• To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

 **How do we protect your information?**

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.  
We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers.  
We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

 **Do we use ‘cookies’?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

 **Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

If you have any question about this privacy policy or your dealings with this website, you may contact us.

Last Edited on 2016-12-14
